It's way too early,
and I haven't even washed my face.
Where are you taking me?
Tell me where we're going at least.
Mr. Kim!
Is it really you?
Are you really, truly my Mr. Kim?
I really am your Mr. Kim.
-Mr. Kim!
-Oh, my.
Did you bring him here?
You need to know how much effort I made.
Then are you staying with me
from now on? Yeah?
Well, Kyeong-do begged me to do so.
But where's the highlight?
Hey… How can I wear that at this age?
You don't know how to throw a surprise.
Gosh…
How am I supposed to put this on?
You yourself are the gift.
It even matches your personal color.
Give it to me.
You want me to?
Just this once.
-Okay. Fine, do it.
-Do it?
Here…
-You look so pretty.
-Really?
It looks good on you, Mr. Kim.
-Yeah, totally!
You… All right.
Now, where to?
Mr. Kim, did you read the articles
about my divorce?
Of course I did. Good job.
I'm proud of you.
You can just live freely
like the people these days,
and if it doesn't work,
just find a new one.
Honestly, you can get married
even three times with that beauty.
I agree with you.
It'd be a shame to waste my beauty.
But three times is too many.
Anyway, have you been keeping in touch
with Kyeong-do?
And together, you missed me?
WINTER, 2015
NAME: LEE HAN-SOO
WISHING YOU A FAST RECOVERY
INPATIENT WARD
-Mr. Kim!
-Hey.
I knew it was you.
I was in the area.
Mr. Kim, I appreciate this, but…
we don't need it.
Take it. I got a lot for my severance pay.
Severance pay?
I quit. It happened.
It's not much. Get something
for your parents to cheer them up.
Thank you.
Kyeong-do.
Life can be stifling
even when we're doing our best, right?
Still, cheer up. That's how you carry on.
Bye. Make sure to eat well.
Okay.
Kyeong-do.
Yeah?
Thank you so much
for bringing back Mr. Kim.
I've never even thought about it.
I did all of this for you--
Let's take my press release photo.
Please?
I feel like facing this side tonight.
Kyeong-do.
Kyeong-do?
If you do it after a punch,
it breaks both our hearts, doesn't it?
Do it when I'm still being nice, okay?
The cell phones these days
have really nice cameras, you know?
Let's take just a few, okay?
I love you, Kyeong-do, yeah?
Yeah? Yeah?
This love is twisted.
I love you, Kyeong-do. Yeah?
Yeah? Yeah? Yeah? Yeah? Yeah? Yeah?
EPISODE 8
So, one more lap?
Didn't you learn about
saving energy when you were little?
I know how the first day at work
makes you tense,
but we've been going around
five times already.
Why don't you just take the bus next time?
Or you can take the subway.
Mr. Kim, hurry up.
I have to use the restroom.
My gosh, so why did you
gulp down all that coffee?
-Hello?
-We're arriving soon. Focus.
Hey, look--
My goodness.
Okay.
Bye.
Good luck!
One more time.
But why is she making me do this?
She's pretty though.
DIRECTOR SEO JI-WOO
OF JARIM APPAREL'S FIRST STEP
JARIM Apparel's PR Team is working hard.
What is it?
"Director Seo Ji-woo
of JARIM Apparel's first step."
This one.
What a nice picture.
Someone in their PR Team must've worked
until their knees got worn out for this.
Who knows if it was their employee,
or someone in love with her?
What?
What are you saying?
Hello?
Hi. I'm calling you
regarding the results for the analysis
-you requested last time.
-Okay.
Didroxin?
Yes, that's what was found.
Well… What is that used for?
It's prescribed
to the Stick Syndrome patients.
Stick Syndrome?
It's a type of chronic vascular disease.
KOREA GENERAL ACADEMIC PAPERS DB
DIDROXIN
It's manageable
as long as they take the medicine,
and the drug doesn't have
any dangerous toxicity.
However, in case of overdose,
it can cause side effects.
So they need to consult the doctor.
What kind of side effects?
Memory loss and cognitive disorder.
The common symptoms of Alzheimer's.
THE SIDE EFFECTS OF DIDROXIN
DAMAGE TO THE CENTRAL NERVOUS SYSTEM
The problem is,
the dosage came out pretty high.
A SERIOUS COGNITIVE DISORDER
HAS ALSO BEEN REPORTED
Hi, Ms. Seo. It's me.
Do you have time to meet?
Come in.
Thank you.
One second.
Don't drink
what the secretaries give you anymore.
The coffee I took last time.
So I can drink it later.
Oh, yes. That.
I actually had it analyzed.
Are you taking Didroxin by chance?
Didroxin…
I think I used to take it in the past.
But I'm taking something else right now.
But why do you ask…
Well…
Can I ask why you changed your medicine?
At the time,
I was on a business trip abroad.
I think my husband said
he was meeting my doctor.
He said the doctor wanted to
change my prescription
because better medicine was released.
But you didn't hear that
directly from your doctor?
No.
Is there a problem with that medicine?
The medicine itself isn't bad.
But it can cause side effects.
I looked up some papers
and consulted medical reporters as well.
And I think it's related
to your Alzheimer's symptoms.
Why is that in my coffee…
Who would…
I doubt it.
He wouldn't do such a…
Nothing is certain.
But you should still be careful.
Don't take any drinks or food
from Secretary Yoo.
Still, if you take nothing from her,
she might notice.
So you need to act naturally
until you have evidence.
You should set up a camera in the pantry.
Okay.
I owe you more and more.
How am I ever going to repay you?
It's just a reporter's hunch.
I didn't do much.
I didn't know you were ill.
All I have to do is just take medicine.
It doesn't affect my daily life.
It's not life-threatening.
How about we talk to Ji-woo about this?
She should know…
Right. I should talk to her.
Would you like to see her before you go?
She probably shouldn't know that I'm here.
You should've waited at home.
I just got here.
Mr. Kim, thank you for your work.
Fix her work fright.
As a more experienced office worker.
Director Seo, I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night, Mr. Kim.
Good night.
-Ready to go?
-Yeah.
Did you have first-day jitters?
Don't even get me started.
I circled around, like, five times.
When there's no oil in this country?
You sound just like Mr. Kim.
He told me to take the bus next time.
Hey, you have to be smart
to take the public transit.
You're too clumsy.
You'd end up crying in the street.
"Waa, I got off at the wrong stop.
Come pick me up."
Hey, go home.
-Go. Go elsewhere.
-"Waa, how am I going to get home?"
Watch out for the stairs and the cars.
Jin-u, go straight to taekwondo.
If you skip it again, you're living here.
-Okay!
-Okay. Bye!
-Bye!
-Bye, guys. Hyo-bin, bye!
Yes, my mom is coming later.
She said she'll dine out with Dong-won.
Yay!
Did you finish it?
Yes, it's inside.
Inside. My wife said it's inside.
-Is that it?
-Yes.
I can't believe she asked for this.
Does Seo Ji-woo think she's a duchess?
Who asks for a portrait these days?
She paid me a lot.
The most I've ever gotten for my painting.
Well, I just sounded her out,
and she sent me the money.
Did you do your best?
I ground my bones.
You should've painted Kyeong-do
as a bonus.
I didn't think about that.
Jeez, you lack the service attitude.
You should've been a businessman.
Why are you acting like this?
Why do you think?
Honestly, asking about
the informant is too--
The informant was Kang Min-woo.
Kang Min-woo… Who is that?
Kang Min-woo gave you
the article about An Da-hye.
JARIM Apparel CEO Seo Ji-yeon's husband.
It was him?
What are you doing?
I didn't receive it from him.
Then who?
Jeez. Hey.
Don't you know me? Come clean,
or you can't walk out that door.
Quick delivery! It was a quick delivery.
I was too embarrassed to say it.
You could've just let it slide.
-Quick delivery?
-Yes! Quick! Quick delivery!
So Reporter Nam,
if you support Reporter Choi
with the interview and email it to me…
-Need any help?
-Where is the Entertainment Team?
You can give that to me. I'm on that team.
-Sign here.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
-Keep me posted, Reporter Choi.
-Okay.
So you gulped down the scoop
sent to the Entertainment Team.
And you avoided me because you hated
the thought of me finding out?
Why would I hate you?
You know I love you so much.
I didn't say anything
so the manager wouldn't be in trouble.
What do you mean?
I reported it to Department Manager.
And she told me not to publish it,
very seriously.
Don't accuse me.
I didn't know that you, Seo Ji-woo,
and Cho Jin-eon were involved.
She probably stopped me because she knew,
but if a reporter ignores a report,
that would be media corruption.
What did I do so wrong?
Taking the exclusive all to myself?
Let's be honest. If you received it,
you would've just killed it.
She told you not to write about it?
Happy now?
So stop harassing me. Can I go now?
Sit down. We've only started.
You can't go anywhere.
What is it now?
You need a follow-up article.
All right. Focus. If that report triggered
an even more vicious setup,
would you be free from it?
Why are you scaring me? Trigger what?
I can't explain right now.
First, go meet An Da-hye with me.
An is looking for you, so you request it.
Are you telling me to meet An?
Are you crazy?
-Why are you surprised?
-Doo-jin is following up on An Da-hye.
I don't know what it is, but don't.
Don't do it.
If you tell me not to do it, I won't.
Please excuse me.
Damn it.
What's he talking about?
Is that yours?
I will report it to you when ready.
-Did you tell him not to write about it?
-Write what?
You know, that article about Cho Jin-eon.
Get out of my way. I don't remember.
She's so loyal.
Department Manager is clearly an F.
There goes the big F.
I did it because you asked.
But you're not going to leave it here,
are you, Ji-woo?
Woo-sik. Did you know
Kyeong-do was the ace in the Culture Team?
I know he was in the Culture Team.
A masterpiece like this
should be in the ace's house.
Don't you think, Se-yeong?
For a masterpiece like this, I think so.
My blood sugar's dropping.
Is meat coming? Where's Kyeong-do?
I don't know.
Why don't you have that first?
It's for Dong-won.
If it's chosen by Ji-woo,
it must be luxurious and delicious.
The meat is coming. Wait for it.
-Yes, ma'am.
-So cute.
-Thank you.
-What is it?
Leave it for the dessert.
Jeong-min.
Mother. Give that to me. Here.
-It's not heavy.
-Give it to me.
Kyeong-do is late
when he's the one who invited everyone.
Is he not home yet?
He asked for kimchi
because you guys were coming.
He said he'd come pick it up,
but he's late.
So his old and busy mom had to bring it.
No. I think he's late on purpose
so he can invite you in too.
So you can see us after a long time.
He's so thoughtful.
Goodness.
Just have fun between you guys.
I don't want to make him a mama's boy.
Kyeong-do's dream is to be a mama's boy.
Come with me.
-No, nonsense.
-Come on.
You go and have fun.
-But--
-Bye.
But…
Thank you for this! Bye.
What's that?
Kyeong-do's mother gave it to me.
It's kimchi.
She said he isn't home yet.
-No.
-What are we doing here without…
Wait a minute. What is this?
Wait, Ji-woo, isn't that--
Isn't the top-tier painting different?
Why are you wasting your talent like this?
Why don't you paint me instead?
I only soak my brushes
when the money's wired to me.
That's right.
I wonder how much Ji-woo wired.
Where did she go?
What the…
-Where is she?
-Ji-woo.
Are you in the bathroom?
SOMANG LAUNDROMAT
Are you here for laundry pickup?
Hello.
The takeout food is still warm.
It looks good.
Where did Ji-woo go?
Over there. Looking elegant.
She'll be back soon. I guess she went out
to buy something. Just eat.
I'm hungry.
It's good.
I bet you bought it because it's good.
Why is he sour?
Stop it.
Hey, face it. Isn't that comedy?
Do you really want to keep that
in your house?
A person usually only looks better
in person or in a picture.
But she looks impeccable
both in person and in the picture.
And when she's painted, she becomes art.
Isn't that rare?
This is so good. Aren't you eating?
Then I'm eating it all.
A bastard like him is rare as well.
Whatever.
-Is it good?
-Let's eat.
This is good!
Well…
-In a department store…
-Yes, a department store.
On the basement floor there…
-The basement. You mean the food section?
-Yes.
There are so many pretty things to eat.
Yes, there are a lot.
Nowadays, I guess everyone has skills.
What looks good also tastes good.
I always wondered
if it'd taste as good as it looked.
When I tried one, it was delicious.
That's probably
why department stores sell them.
Yeah, the desserts are very nice
these days.
Some of them are as expensive
as a whole meal.
Some are more expensive than jjajangmyeon.
Things like these
also require a lot of work.
It's not easy to bake things.
When I was debating
between a laundromat and a bakery,
I tried to learn baking,
I couldn't do it. It was so hard.
I heard kneading the dough is very hard…
-That's what I've heard.
-Yes.
Kyeong-do is probably looking for you.
You should go now.
Oh, well, Mothe…
Well…
I'm not sure how to address you.
-Me?
-Yes.
Well, in a drama,
if someone they don't like
calls them "Mother,"
they go, "I'm not your Mother."
I've seen that before.
It'd be funny to call me Mrs. Jo.
Se-yeong and the other boys
all call me Mother.
Just feel free.
I'll drop the honorifics too.
Thank you.
It's not like I don't like you.
Goodness.
I should give the rest
to Kyeong-do's father.
I'll buy you more next time.
All the delicious stuff
on the department store basement floor.
The ones that look pretty.
Well… Mother.
Well, I…
happened to meet Kyeong-do again
after many events.
Well…
I do have a sense of shame.
But I can't help it.
Kyeong-do is right before my eyes.
I can't tell my heart
not to fall for him.
I'm sorry.
That's why couples elope at night.
They elope
because they have no other choice.
Let's go.
I know the shortcut. I'll take you there.
Sorry. I can't hold my laughter…
How are you two going to clean that up?
We'll help.
Not two. Only one idiot will do it.
Honey, paint Jeong-min too.
This will go on for ten years.
Send me the money. Bye.
-Congratulations on your first day.
-Congrats!
I thought we already celebrated
her first day.
Why don't you just sleep over?
Why don't you just get it off your chest?
-Hey, can't you read the room?
-Seriously.
Jeez, you idiot. Seriously.
Leave now. Bye.
He told me to stay.
-Forget it.
-Put your shoes on.
-You can sleep on the street. Now, go.
-This way.
Let's go. Good night!
The earth finally became quiet.
Oh, gosh…
Sit down and get some rest.
-Can I?
-Yeah.
What did you do with my mom?
Wait, how did you know?
Where else would you go
with Dong-won's cupcakes?
You are a reporter after all. What a pro.
So what did you do?
We had the cupcakes, we talked a little,
and she walked me here.
Talked about what?
About the desserts
on the department store basement floor.
Your mother and I
have the same sense of humor.
I have a very important meeting tomorrow.
-All the scary executives will be there.
-What's on the agenda?
Getting rid of MANZAAR.
MANZAAR?
MANZAAR is the symbol of JARIM,
Director Seo.
You know the former chairman cherished it.
Yes, I'm well aware.
But we need to face
that the sales are declining every year.
Yet we're relying on the outlets.
And in the past couple of years,
we've been relying on the home shopping.
Do you also agree with it, Ms. Seo?
Does getting rid of MANZAAR…
sound like erasing Dad?
It's a little…
It kind of feels that way.
If you say it's wrong, I won't do it.
You are the one in charge of
JARIM's 2nd generation after all.
If… you're not comfortable with it,
I won't cause trouble.
I guess Dad wanted to see
this side of you, Ji-woo.
Not tied down, direct, and bold.
Let's get into trouble.
I'm proposing that we launch
a fine-dining restaurant.
Korea also should have
a homegrown high-end luxury brand,
and JARIM is in the position
to lead that initiative.
A high-end luxury brand?
That will require a lot of time
and budget.
That's right.
Even if we start now,
it won't be guaranteed until I turn 60.
But if we scout a renowned designer,
I think we have a chance.
Well,
you should suggest something realistic.
I understand it's unfamiliar
and that you feel anxious.
Because I've only started,
I might not be on track and make a fu…
My suggestions may sound unrealistic.
I'll come up with a detailed suggestion.
Detailed…
Good luck.
Thank you.
Nothing in particular.
If you take the medicine regularly,
you won't have to worry
even in the long run.
Is the new medicine more effective?
The Didroxin I'd prescribed before
wasn't less effective.
But there was a side-effect issue.
My husband told me about it,
but I wasn't paying attention.
What kind of side effects
were you worried about?
As it began to damage
the central nervous system,
I suggested changing the medicine.
I think
you were on a business trip abroad,
so you weren't able to come.
Yes. I remember.
Fortunately, it was noticed early enough
and it was still recoverable.
But if you had continued,
it would've led to Alzheimer's.
Fortunately…
Then I'll book you in
for six months later.
Thank you.
-Doctor.
-Yeah?
What if I kept taking
a lot more of that drug?
Is it impossible to recover?
If Alzheimer's disease is already ongoing,
is it recoverable?
If you're aware of it and stop taking it,
it won't get worse.
And it'd still be in the early stages,
so you don't need to worry.
Are you still anxious?
Then do you want me to book an exam?
No.
When I think about it, it's scary.
Thank you.
Hey, look at this.
This is a list of designers
who are currently in the business…
What is that attitude?
MANZAAR was your father's favorite line.
How can you get rid of MANZAAR?
Gosh, I hear that so much, seriously.
You bloodless, tearless jerk.
Whatever. Look at this.
DESIGNER PROFILE
This is Lucas. He's leaving this brand
after this S/S season.
So you're going to scout that grandpa?
This old man is too much of a big shot.
So instead,
this person.
His successor?
Lucas has two senior designers
and Bella Jin is one of them.
She's the successor nominee.
If she's a nominee,
then it's probably too late.
She's Korean.
Though she's an Australian citizen.
If we appeal to her with patriotism…
Don't induce patriotism in everything.
Besides, if a Korean designer
became a lead designer of Pirco,
that also means a lot.
Can you call yourself a reporter
with that attitude?
Dongwoon Daily is hopeless.
Their assistant manager is idle.
-How can you get an exclusive?
-Good point.
Bella Jin or Lucas, what does that have to
do with a Dongwoon Daily reporter?
Let's order some fried chicken.
You know, that article with Chaos
to prove our dating rumor was groundless…
You didn't read the article.
I never used any cowardly word
like "groundless."
Yeah, whatever.
Anyway, the editor-in-chief
at your fashion magazine. Do you know her?
Let's just order fried chicken.
I don't work for you.
Your discipline is slipping, soldier.
Ji-woo, have you ever served in the army?
All major fashion figures will be
in Samseong-dong next week.
I have to be there.
Bella Jin might be there.
Then say you're a resident and join them.
I'm hungry!
How can I say I'm a resident
and go in there? Jesus.
That's a relief.
It's not going to get any worse.
So I'm not going to tell Ji-woo.
Don't you think that's the reason
why you could tell Ji-woo--
Ji-woo is working on an important project.
This might be just in my head,
but I feel better these days.
Maybe later, when Ji-woo's not too busy.
Maybe then.
Good sleep will help you recover.
I read it in some paper.
I know it sounds too obvious,
but you need to recover perfectly soon.
You should have a good night's sleep.
Yes.
You're welcome. Bye.
-Is someone sick?
-My goodness. Damn it.
Quit it. You're going to get sick.
Hey, you know Kim Ga-eul,
the editor-in-chief?
I wouldn't know. I've never met her.
She collaborated with the manager, not me.
So I don't know her.
I knew that you wouldn't know.
Don't be so arrogant when you don't know.
I knew you were never helpful, jeez.
When the luxury brands staff gather,
you know?
It's best to follow Kim Ga-eul
for the luxury brand business prospect.
I have Han-kyeong.
I must've gone crazy.
Why am I discussing this with you
and not Han-Kyeong?
Lee Kyeong-do, did you pee your pants?
Stomachache?
Unbelievable.
The article on Louis went well
thanks to Ji-woo, no?
Yes. So what?
She needs our help,
so we should cooperate.
You mean you, not we.
I mean, is this how we work?
When we've received help,
we should at least return the favor.
Seriously, I'm so sick of it…
What do you want?
Well, first of all…
First of all, what?
Hey, check this out.
2025 NEW SCOOTER, WHITE
That one. Hey, that's pretty.
A whole different level.
White is the safe color. Let's get this.
Are you really paying?
You barely make anything
after paying for the rental.
But still. This is too expensive.
Don't do it.
You need confidence
in the world of delivery.
With this, no one will dare to touch you.
No one comes at me even now.
For goodness' sake. So it's a no?
You don't want it?
White. White is pretty.
White is pretty, right?
It's an investment.
If you thrive later,
you have to hire me as a manager.
You're quite good
at the entertainment business.
It's a very good investment, CEO Lee.
It's all thanks to you, Actor Cha.
-You must do well, okay?
-Thank you, sir!
Why did you meet my corporate lawyers?
I met them for legal advice.
What for? All the noise has been settled.
Are you in trouble again?
Oh, no, that's not it.
I've only been exercising and staying low.
Then what's the problem?
You need to be honest with me
so I can help you settle it!
Father, I…
Father. I want to get back with Ji-woo.
You should've behaved then.
But why do you need legal advice for that?
Just go beg on your knees.
Well, I was…
I was asking
if I could cancel the divorce.
Cancel it?
Yes, Father, this is so unfair.
She wanted a divorce,
and set me up with her affair partner…
An affair partner?
-No, it's--
-An affair?
No, Father.
Lucas's successor might not be Bella Jin?
All right. The designer whom Lucas trusts
is indeed Bella Jin.
But the rumor says the owner is eyeing
Judy Wong more than Bella Jin.
Only someone like me
can find information like this--
How is that possible?
I heard Bella Jin was more competent.
Then who's coming to the event?
Did you secure the list?
How can I do that?
I got this information because it's me--
Is Bella Jin coming?
-She's not coming for sure.
-Why not?
On vacation. She's in Málaga.
Málaga… Where is that?
In Spain. That's where she goes
for her vacation every year.
And she only stays in the same place.
My editor-in-chief went there once before.
Anyway, she's there.
Where in Málaga?
-I wouldn't know.
-You have to know.
The editor-in-chief doesn't know
the address either.
It's on the top floor
of a five-story building.
She walked up a spiraling staircase,
and the first floor was an ice cream shop.
Ice cream…
Why are you rolling your eyes?
You're scaring me.
-What are you doing?
-Don't talk to me. I can't multitask.
I found it. Give me your passport.
Why do you need my passport?
To meet Bella Jin.
Am I going alone?
That far? So lonely and forlorn?
What about my own schedule?
I'm the son of Dongwoon,
Assistant Manager Lee.
He's absent today,
and he took four days off.
Shall I look up Seo Ji-woo's schedule?
Does he think he's a fashion person?
I am a fashion person, right?
He used his precious vacation days?
Has he left already?
If he's going away for six days,
he must be going abroad.
What?
Who am I talking to?
What are you having for lunch?
I want malatang.
You said you wanted pasta earlier.
Let's have Chinese food.
Sorry, all, let's have Chinese food.
Seriously, why did he have to leave…
Reporter Choi,
find a delicious Chinese restaurant
that makes good malatang.
Hey, think about quitting
and working as Ji-woo's secretary.
You know the saying,
"Saving turns things into poop"?
I saved my vacation days
only to waste them on this.
Have you heard the phrase,
"smiling bastard"?
That probably means her, right?
She's not that annoying.
You haven't met a real bastard yet.
Nothing.
Yeah, let's go.
Have a good trip.
DIRECTOR KANG MIN-WOO
Are they ever going to grow up?
Shouldn't a reporter know better?
I see why Bella Jin comes here
for vacation every year.
About Bella Jin,
since she's vacationing
in a beautiful place like this,
she'd fall for my offer, right?
Is someone coming from the hotel?
Wouldn't it be faster if we went?
I think she's nearby.
Here.
-Hello.
Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
Hello, nice to meet you.
If we're staying at the host's house…
There's no hotel around here.
I searched for a place to stay
near Bella Jin until my eyes were sore.
You know?
It's not easy to find accommodation.
But I don't have any good memories
with accommodations found like this.
Maybe when you booked it.
This is about discernment.
I'll let you have breakfast
on the sea-view terrace. It's awesome.
An alley like this wouldn't give an angle
for a sea view.
Honey, they are here.
Hello.
-Hello.
You can get ahead of yourself
internationally.
I'm not. You can see the sea.
What else I'm supposed to say?
Right. We're not here for the sea view.
We're here for Bella Jin.
Do you want to go here?
Where is it?
We're on this side.
"Amore Gelato…" That's down here…
-Do you see this?
-Around here?
Yeah.
Let's try that way.
-Hello.
It's a three-story.
-Do you want to get something? Come on.
-But…
It's a five-story.
Stay here. Your legs will get tired.
Is this the one?
It's just a house, not an accommodation.
Go wait at a cafe somewhere.
I'll look for it. It shouldn't take long.
I'd be dead from waiting.
You'll carry me if I got too tired.
That'd be too much.
-A gelato shop.
-What?
Five stories too.
I'm getting a good feeling about it.
Sit here. I'll go check.
Is this the one?
This is the one.
-Where is Bella Jin?
-Wait.
She went to Barcelona.
She'll be back tomorrow.
I gave my number to the landlord.
She'll call us when she's back.
Okay…
-She'll be back tomorrow, right?
-What?
-Holy shit.
-What is it?
This is the same as the play.
"Mr. Godot will surely come tomorrow."
But he never comes, and the play ends--
Calm down.
Bella Jin won't come tonight.
But surely tomorrow.
Let's believe it. Who knows?
She might come tonight.
Then what are we doing today?
We'll check out Málaga.
We're tourists today. Okay?
But what if she doesn't--
Seriously. Let's go.
We found this building. Okay?
That's true.
Shall we eat first?
-Yes.
-Let's go.
Let's come here again for vacation later.
Depending on where we're staying.
How many times did I tell you?
It was the closest to Bella Jin's--
I'm sure there was a better one.
You know my real intention.
Stop bullshitting.
So what is your real intention?
The place we're staying might feel tight.
But on the other hand, it's cozy.
Exotic coziness.
The bed is also big. It's a double bed.
If I fall while turning,
I'd get a fracture.
There was a time when a single bed
was enough for both of us, you woman.
What do we do now?
Picasso's birthplace is here.
Are we on a school trip?
If we have a beer now… It'd be perfect.
-Eat this.
-I've had enough. Too sweet.
Don't you ever crave alcohol?
It's not that I don't think about it.
The taste you know is the scariest.
I'd just suppress it until I die.
I can do it.
Even if it is scary,
if you suppress it, I'll do it too.
Let's go.
What do you want to do?
There is Picasso's birthplace.
No, only high schoolers go there.
Those two assholes are having
a secret affair abroad?
And how did you know
and send me the pictures?
You know… I'm heartbroken.
I couldn't just ignore it.
You couldn't get over Ji-woo and wanted
to get back with her. You sounded sincere.
But she's living with someone?
I only dug into her to tell you
that you were mistaken, but…
I was right, wasn't I?
They fucked me up, right?
What are you going to do?
I can't take anyone's side. My goodness.
But, Min-woo, you know what?
I pity her. Get it?
When I think about Seo Ji-woo, I pity her.
My father said
if I ever mention Seo Ji-woo again,
he won't leave me anything, shit.
I even knelt down to get back with her.
Gosh, you are amazing.
"Why accept her again
when Chairman Seo is dead?"
"Who knows whose child she is?
I only accepted her for Chairman Seo."
"Don't you dare bring her back,
you idiot!" He said.
What are you saying?
Gosh.
I guess I really loved her, Min-woo.
Who?
He doesn't know who is whose child?
Her! Seo Ji-woo!
She's not the daughter of
JARIM Apparel's Chairman Seo Won-seok.
Her mom had her from an affair.
Can you believe that?
Shit.
That's nonsense. Shit.
Let's go.
That looks fun.
What?
A European flea market.
That looks romantic.
Let's check it out.
What is that? A ski?
The cookies look good.
-Hello.
I already had two ice creams.
Right.
Then go ahead. I'll catch up with you.
Okay.
SEO JI-WOO
It's five euro.
What?
What's wrong?
No, I think I grabbed it first.
We kind of grabbed it at the same time.
Wait, this is…
Ji-woo.
You said you grabbed it first.
Ninety-eight limited scarves
according to the two-piece suit.
You know it.
I used to look down on JARIM,
but you're not bad.
Who are you?
Are you
Bella Jin?
Come on.
My ace is working his ass off in Málaga.
He's your ace. Not mine.
Seriously?
Your ace. What was his name again?
Wi-do?
He had a unique name.
Kyeong-do.
Not Wi-do. Kyeong-do.
Right. Kyeong-do. Kim Kyeong-do.
Which Kim clan?
It's not Kim. It's Lee.
Is that so? Is he a Lee? What a relief.
I get along with the Lees so much.
I had the tarot card reading.
I was told I get along with the Lees.
He has no double eyelids, right?
A man with no double eyelids--
-Hey!
-What?
Where is Bella Jin?
Honey, how much more
do you expect me to do?
I told you everything I found.
That Bella Jin's on vacation
and the location, everything.
An ice cream shop on the 1st floor
in a five-story building?
Can you find a person abroad with that?
You can't?
You're so brazen.
I told you so much already.
Hold on.
Right now, in Spain, it's…
Hey, Bella Jin can answer her phone.
Too musty. Stress.
Hey, do you think
that jacket goes with that shirt?
Just putting on whatever you grab,
you need to fix that first.
Hey! Stop changing the topic.
I'll make it clear for you.
Call Bella Jin now.
Give her my ace's number.
Tell Bella Jin to call him first.
I should go on with this color.
Seriously,
I'm a very pure person.
Getting Bella Jin's location
over a mere friendship.
If I ever get involved with you again,
I'll either quit this editor-in-chief job
or quit our friendship.
See? She's not answering.
How many times do I tell you
that we're not close?
Oh, my Bella, where are you?
Did she pick up? Awesome. So shocking.
Oh, my. In Barcelona?
Hey, tell her to go to Málaga.
My dear Bella, are you in Barcelona?
Isn't that nice?
Hey, cut to the chase.
When are you going to Málaga, honey?
Holding back is a strategy.
-Are you getting teary?
-Not funny.
No way she could scout
a luxury brand designer.
Have you ever liked any other woman?
I have.
You're groundbreaking in so many ways.
Then are you moving on?
How come we've never run into each other?
Waiting for Godot is over.
Everything is over.
He said he'd come if I waited. Bullshit.
The curtain's closed.
My Kyeong-do idiot should end it too.